wpthemespress.com 2012-08-29

# 5 Shades Templates - Privacy Policy

5ShadesTemplates.com, Inc. (hereafter referred to as 5ShadesTemplates.com) has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to the privacy of the users of our websites. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users. 

###  What this Privacy Policy Covers  

This privacy policy covers 5ShadesTemplates.com's treatment of personally identifiable information collected by 5ShadesTemplates.com through a website owned and operated by 5ShadesTemplates.com. 

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that 5ShadesTemplates.com does not own or control, or of persons that 5ShadesTemplates.com does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which 5ShadesTemplates.com websites link. 

### Collection and Use of Personal Information  

Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. 5ShadesTemplates.com will use this information to reply to your inquiries, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member's account, and to contact you regarding new products and services. 

By accessing the services of 5ShadesTemplates.com and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

### Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information  

5ShadesTemplates.com automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. 5ShadesTemplates.com may use this information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, 5ShadesTemplates.com does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you. 

5ShadesTemplates.com also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and 5ShadesTemplates.com assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure  

• 5ShadesTemplates.com may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of 5ShadesTemplates.com to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these purposes only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information 

• 5ShadesTemplates.com may otherwise disclose your personal information when: 

  * We have your express consent to share the information for a specified purpose;
  * We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process; 
  * We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of 5ShadesTemplates.com; 
  * We find that your actions on our websites violate the 5ShadesTemplates.com Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

### Consent 

• If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to 5ShadesTemplates.com. If you have provided personal information to 5ShadesTemplates.com and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify 5ShadesTemplates.com at privacy@templatemonster.com. 

### Security 

• Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, your 5ShadesTemplates.com Information protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, 5ShadesTemplates.com uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

• We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures. 

• Further, 5ShadesTemplates.com retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes identified above or as required by law. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy  

• 5ShadesTemplates.com may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of 5ShadesTemplates.com websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof. 

### Questions or Suggestions 

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at [privacy@5shadestemplates.com](mailto:privacy@5shadestemplates.com).
